<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Glimesh Handbook</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/</link><description>Recent content on Glimesh Handbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 08:57:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://handbook.glimesh.tv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teams</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/teams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 08:57:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/teams/</guid><description>Glimesh is an open company with the following teams, each with their own mission and scope. Members can be a part of many teams, or a single team.
Core The core team is the glue that binds all the teams together and builds the company as a whole. Culture, branding, mission, and other high level goals are set by the core team.
Other responsibilities:
Accounting Business Partnerships Governance Glimesh Community Team The GCT is a group of volunteer supporters of the platform, and it&amp;rsquo;s vision.</description></item><item><title>Deploying the Site</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/engineering/deploying-the-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:39:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/engineering/deploying-the-site/</guid><description>Currently the deployment is a bit of a manual process. We&amp;rsquo;re utilizing Elixir Releases inside of a docker container for dependency management and portability.
No state is stored on the host machine besides a couple of environment variables.
How to Deploy git pull docker-compose build docker-compose down &amp;amp;&amp;amp; docker-compose up -d</description></item><item><title>Mission</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:39:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/mission/</guid><description>Our mission at Glimesh is to create a platform where every content creator has an opportunity to shine! We believe that the path to growth for all is by building a platform that puts the streamers &amp;amp; community first, not the advertisers.</description></item><item><title>Values</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/values/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:39:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/values/</guid><description>Transparency We believe that secrets don’t make friends and we should all have an equal voice in how the services we use are made.
Community Together, we’re better.
Equality We believe all content creators, big or small, regardless of what they stream, deserve an equal chance at recognition for their hard work.</description></item></channel></rss>