<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Company on Glimesh Handbook</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/</link><description>Recent content in Company on Glimesh Handbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 08:01:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ownership</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/ownership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 08:01:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/ownership/</guid><description>Glimesh, Inc. is an open company, which explains how we operate the business. However Glimesh is not a non-profit, or public company, instead it is a privately owned C Corporation registered in the state of Delaware. Glimesh, Inc. is currently wholly owned by Luke Strickland.
Ownership Stakes Luke Strickland - 100%
Future Ownership Plan There&amp;rsquo;s much about the ownership of Glimesh that we hope to change over time. Ideally we can build a hybrid company that embraces all of the required-transparency benefits of a non-profit, the original &amp;ldquo;price to cost&amp;rdquo; ideals of Gittip, and the compensation of correctly managed for-profit companies.</description></item><item><title>Open Company</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/open-company/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 07:58:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/open-company/</guid><description>Glimesh, Inc. is a new type of company, an open company. For Glimesh, this means that we develop all of our products publicly, from planning to development. All software we write is open source, and it&amp;rsquo;s active usage by others is encouraged. Our intellectual property is developed in the open and is published for all. We regularly share financial reports and other company data, without compromising customer privacy.
The line of transparency is an easy one to walk when you embrace a couple of key points:</description></item><item><title>Teams</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/teams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 08:57:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/teams/</guid><description>Glimesh is an open company with the following teams, each with their own mission and scope. Members can be a part of many teams, or a single team.
Core The core team is the glue that binds all the teams together and builds the company as a whole. Culture, branding, mission, and other high level goals are set by the core team.
Other responsibilities:
Accounting Business Partnerships Governance Glimesh Community Team The GCT is a group of volunteer supporters of the platform, and it&amp;rsquo;s vision.</description></item><item><title>Mission</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:39:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/mission/</guid><description>Our mission at Glimesh is to create a platform where every content creator has an opportunity to shine! We believe that the path to growth for all is by building a platform that puts the streamers &amp;amp; community first, not the advertisers.</description></item><item><title>Values</title><link>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/values/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:39:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://handbook.glimesh.tv/company/values/</guid><description> This description of the values are currently in progress.
Community Fairness Service Sustainability Transparency</description></item></channel></rss>